Inventory of the Records of Joseph Dupuy Eggleston 1913-1919
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Series I
  - Saunders, C.W.; Saunders, E.W.; Sheperd, B.M. 1915 (Box-folder 3-246)
  - Smith, H.L. Gov; Stuart H.C. 1915 (Box-folder 3-247)
  - Stiles, H.R.; Stone, M.E.; Strode, A.E. 1917 (Box-folder 3-248)
  - Swanson, Claude A. 1914-1915 (Box-folder 3-249)
  - S--Miscellaneous 1915 (Box-folder 3-250)
    Commonwealth of Virginia
  - T--Miscellaneous 1915 (Box-folder 3-251)
  - Campbell, T.P. 1913-1915 (Box-folder 3-252)
    Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Office of the Dean of Faculty; Lewis-Gale Hospital
  - Carrier, Lyman 1912-1914 (Box-folder 3-253)
    Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Department of Biology; Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Office of the President; Virginia Agrilculture Experiment Station
  - Chrisman, W.G. 1913-1915 (Box-folder 3-254)
    Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Department of Veterinary Science
  - Contracts and Agreements 1913-1914 (Box-folder 3-255)
  - Cutchins, C.A. 1914-1915 (Box-folder 3-256)
    Norfolk and Western Railway Company; Notable letterhead from the (Roanoke) World News; Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Office of the President; Notable letterhead from Southern Express Company; Notable letterhead from Richmond Evening Journal
  - (Virginia Polytechnic Institute) Department Appropriations, Salary Increases 1915-1916 (Box-folder 3-257)
    Department of Experimental Engineering; Department of Metallurgy and Metallography; Department of Mathematics; Department of Electrical Engineering; School of Graphics; Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station; Shops Department
  - Davidson, R.J. 1913-1915 (Box-folder 3-258)
    Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Department of Chemistry; Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Office of the Dean of Faculty
  - Ellet, Robert 1913 (Box-folder 3-259)
    Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Office of the Secretary of the Faculty
  - Ellison, B. 1913-1915 (Box-folder 3-260)
    Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Dining Hall Department; Notable letterhead from Harris, Woodson Co. Inc.; The Bugle
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute; Faculty Matters 1913-1915 (Box-folder 3-261)
    Office of the President; Department of Modern Languages; Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station; Department of Mechanical Engineering; Shops Department; Department of Electrical Engineering; Department of Biology; Department of Experiemtnal Engineering; Department of Chemistry; Department of Mining Engineering; Department of Physics; Department of Geology; Department of English; Department of Rhetoric; Department of Civil Engineering; Department of Metallurgy and Metallography; Department of Mathematics; Department of Veterinary Scince; School of Graphics
- Series II 1912-1919
  - Fogleman, J.B. 1913-1915 (Box-folder 4-262)
    Virginia Agricultural Experiemtn Station
  - F.D. Fromme; T.B. Hutcheson 1914-1915 (Box-folder 4-263)
    Virginia Agricultural Experiement Station; New York State Department of Health; Commonwealth of Massachusttes--State Board of Insanity
  - U-V--Miscellaneous 1915 (Box-folder 4-264)
  - Williams, A.B.--B.S.--John 1915 (Box-folder 4-265)
    Commonwealth of Virginia, House of Delegates
  - War Department 1915 (Box-folder 4-266)
  - Wilson, James S. 1915 (Box-folder 4-267)
  - Winston, J.R. 1915 (Box-folder 4-268)
  - Word, Q.M. 1914-1915 (Box-folder 4-269)
  - W--miscellaneous 1914-1915 (Box-folder 4-270)
    Commonwealth of Virginia, Department of the State Corporation Commission; Co-Operative Education Association
  - Yerby, Emma--Blacksburg High School 1915 (Box-folder 4-271)
  - S.W. Anding; H.M. Arnold 1914-1915 (Box-folder 4-272)
    Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Office of the Commandant
  - "Uncle Bill" (Box-folder 4-273)
    Southern Express Company
  - Appropriations--J.D.E. 1914 (Box-folder 4-274)
    Letter to the appropriations Committee regarding College of William and Mary holding summer sessions at VPI; Commonwealth of Virginia, House of Delegates; Commonwealth of Virginia, Senate Chamber; Letterhead from Algoma Orchards; State Board of Education, Department of Public Instruction; Notable letterhead from The Register
  - Begg, Professor R.B.H. (Department of Civil Engineering) 1913-1915 (Box-folder 4-275)
    Sewage disposal plant for college and town; Proposed highway engineering curse; Estimated expenses of Engineering Department, 1914-1915
  - Brainerd, Walter Kirk (professor of Dairy Husbandry) 1913-1914 (Box-folder 4-276)
    Department of Dairying and Animal Husbandry; Virginia Agricultural Experiemtn Station; Organization of Animal Husbandry Department; History of infection abortion in the VPI herd; Letter re commercial management of Dairy Husbandry, Animal Husbandry, Farm, and Creamery Departments
  - Chrisman, W.G. 1916 (Box-folder 4-277)
    Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Department of Veterinary Science--appropriation
  - Ferneyhough, J.G., State Veterinarian 1902, 1914-1916 (Box-folder 4-278)
    Status opf Commonwealth of Virginia, Office of State Veterinarian; Invitation to the State Veterinary Medical Association Luncheon
  - Holden, R.J. (Department of Geology) 1913-1915 (Box-folder 4-279)
    Natural Occurence of copper ore under buildings; College water supply; Automatic signals for classes; Proposals for Department of Geology, including museum; Letterhead for Congre`s Ge`ologique International
  - Holdaway, C.W. 1913-1915 (Box-folder 4-280)
    Virginia Polytechnic Institute, College of Agrilculture and Experiment Station; VPI Creamery balance sheet, 1912-1913; Skimming station at Vawter's Store; Annual Report, VPI Creamery
  - Hudnall, R.H. 1913-1915 (Box-folder 4-281)
    "The VPI and Arbor Day," Virginia Polytechnic Institute begins annual Arbor Day Festivities
  - Hutcheson, Thomas B. 1914-1915 (Box-folder 4-282)
  - Hunt, R.E. (Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station) 1914-1915 (Box-folder 4-283)
    Stock judging contest proposed; Proposed expenditures for livestock management
  - Johnson, J.M. (Shops Department, Virginia Polyechnic Institute) 1915 (Box-folder 4-284)
  - Johnson, J.S.A. 1913-1915 (Box-folder 4-285)
    Expenditures of the Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Department of Experimental Engineering; Letter from C.E. Allen, Westinghouse Electric & Manufacturing Company; Virginia Polytechnic Institute, General Alumni Association, Secretary's Office; Apparatus needed for Department of Applied Mechanics and Experiemtnal Engineering; Letter regarding improvements underway at VPI (July 29, 1914); Letter regarding upcoming address by Jackson Davis on "industrial side of public school work for negroes"
  - Jones, Eleanor I.; Lee, Claudius 1913-1915 (Box-folder 4-286)
    Assistant librarian position and salary; Letter to Claudius Lee (Department of electrical Engineering) regarding need for uniform system of central time
  - McBryde, J.B. (Department of Chemistry) 1912-1915 (Box-folder 4-286)
    Proposed remodeling of Professor McBryde's cottage; Statement of present condition and needs of the Chemical Department (June 1914); Chart of cost per year of operating VPI Chemical Department for session 1912-1913 with similar deartments at other institutions
  - Mattews, D.O. (Superintendent of Grounds and Building) 1913-1915 (Box-folder 4-288)
    Ststement of need of funds for repair of college buildings (January 1914); Water works department appropriations; Expenditures on the new shops; Septic tank constructions; Power plant service; Library heating
  - Miles, C.P. 1913-1915 (Box-folder 4-289)
    Virginia Polytechnic Institute Athletic Association; Financial Standing of the Field House; Proposed funds for permanent athletic bulidings
  - Needs of Departments, Virginia Polytechnic Institute 1915-1916 (Box-folder 4-290)
    Virginia Agricultural Experiemtn Station; Engineering Division; Department of Veterinary Science; School of Mining Engineering; Farm Machinery; Letter from Mississippi Agricultural and Mechanical College regarding Farm Machinery Course; United States Department of Agriculture, Bureau of animanl Industry regarding poultry industry; Dairy and Animal Husbandry Departments; Need for poultry work; Need for Agricultural Engineering Department; Office of D.O. Matthews, Superintendent of Grounds and Buildings, Heat and Power, Electric Light Department, Water Works, Campus, Steam Laundry regarding power plant needs; Registrar's chart of matriculates, 1911-1912 to 1915-1916
  - Newman, C.M. 1914-1915 (Box-folder 4-291)
    Needs of Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Department of Rhetoric
  - Parrott, John Robert 1913-1915 (Box-folder 4-292)
    Letter regarding erection of Shops Department of Virginia Polytechnic Institute; Repairs of various buildings; Shop work in Civil Engineering course; Repair funds
  - Price, Harvey Lee, Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station 1913-1915 (Box-folder 4-293)
  - Pritchard, Samuel Reynolds 1913-1914 (Box-folder 4-294)
    Apparatus and equipment needed for Department of electrical Engineering; Virginia Polytechnic Institute Alumni Association
  - Randolph, Lingan Strother 1913-1915 (Box-folder 4-295)
    Notable letterhead from the American Society of Mechanical Engineers; Needs of Virginia Polytechnic Institute Department of Mechanical Engineering; VPI Student branch of the American Society of Engineers; Economic management of the power plant
  - Rasche, William Henry; Reed howard S.; Robeson, F.L. 1913-1915 (Box-folder 4-296)
    Letterhead, Virginia Polytechnic Institute, School of Graphics; Virginia Agricultural Experiemtn Station--dogs on campus, college spring
  - Saunders, W.D. 1913-1915 (Box-folder 4-297)
    Letter from Commonwealth of Virginia, Department of Agrilculture and Immigration, Dairy and Food Division regarding testing cows for tuberculosis; Board of Visitors, July 23, 1914
  - Schoene, W.J. 1913-1915 (Box-folder 4-298)
    Commonwealth of Virginia, Office of the State Crop Pest Commission, Crop Pest Law; Gernsey bull controversy
  - Schultz, j.H.; Smyth, Ellison A..J. 1913-1915 (Box-folder 4-299)
    Needs of Virginia Polytechnic Institute Department of Biology for 1914-1915; List of the more important trees and shrubs on VPI campus
  - Starcher, G.C.; Summers, L.W., associate professor of Animal Husbandry; 1909, 1913-1915 (Box-folder 4-300)
  - Vawter, C.E. 1913-1915 (Box-folder 4-301)
    Appropriations for the Virginia Polytechnic Institute Department of Physics
  - Ware, J.F. 1913-1914 (Box-folder 4-302)
    Question of permitting cadets to go to the library after "call to quarters"
  - Watson, J.W. 1913 (Box-folder 4-303)
  - Agriculture Report--Koiner, G.W. 1916 (Box-folder 4-304)
  - Anding, S.W., Commandant (Box-folder 4-305)
    Value of student military training; Notable letterhead from the Bugle, 1916 with request to move drill hour; Cadets claim the right o have two lights in their room; Organization of VPI regiment; Quality of mess hall fare
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute Appropriations 1916 (Box-folder 4-306)
    Office of the Commandant, Shops Department; Department of Chemistry; Department of Veterinary Science; General Alumni Association, Executive Secretary's Office; Department of Rhetoric; Department of Biology; Office of the Dean of Faculty; Virginia Agricultural Experiemtn Station; Department of Mechanical Engineering; W.L. Andrews, Commonwealth of Virginia, Senate Chamber
  - Barlow, W.E., Department of Metallurgy and Metalography 1916 (Box-folder 4-307)
    Davidson house
  - Begg, R.B.H., Department of Civil Engineering 1916 (Box-folder 4-308)
    Sewage disposal plant
  - Blacksburg High School 1916 (Box-folder 4-309)
  - Byrds--Dick and Harry, Commonwealth of Virginia Commission on Economy and Efficiency 1916 (Box-folder 4-310)
  - Campbell, T.P., Dean of Faculty 1916 (Box-folder 4-311)
  - Campbell, T.P. Jr. Registrar 1916 (Box-folder 4-312)
    Letter regarding inspection of other colleges
  - Clayton, Graham 1916 (Box-folder 4-313)
  - Conner, W.G. 1916 (Box-folder 4-314)
    Equipment for Shops Department of Virginia Polytechnic Institute
  - Co-Operative Education Association of Virginia (Field Work) 1916 (Box-folder 4-315)
  - Davis, Westmoreland 1916 (Box-folder 4-316)
  - Degree Policies 1916 (Box-folder 4-317)
  - Drinkard, A.W. 1916 (Box-folder 4-318)
  - Eleart, F.W., Mayor 1913-1914, 1916 (Box-folder 4-319)
    Letter regarding town spring; Topics Incude arc lamps, conditions of water, septic tank
  - Faculty Matters 1915-1916, 1918 (Box-folder 4-320)
  - F.D. Fromme, Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station 1916 (Box-folder 4-321)
  - Gibboney, J.H. (Norfolk and Western Railway Company) 1916 (Box-folder 4-322)
  - Gudheim, H. (School of Graphics) 4-323 (Box-folder 4-323)
  - Hart, Harris 1916 (Box-folder 4-324)
  - Hill, H.H., General Alumni Association, Virginia Polytechnic Institute, General Secretry's Office 1916 (Box-folder 4-325)
  - Hodgson, E.R. 1916 (Box-folder 3-326)
    Proposed machinery hall; High School girls and boys basketball teams use of the field house
  - Holdaway, C.W. 1916 (Box-folder 4-327)
    Creamery Matters
  - Holden, R.J. (Department of Geology) 1916 (Box-folder 4-328)
  - Hunt, R.E., Animal Husbandman 1916 (Box-folder 4-329)
    Students aggravating the bulls
  - Hutcheson, T.B. 1913, 1916 (Box-folder 4-330)
    Lady wants course in agriculture
  - Johnson, J.S.A. 1916 (Box-folder 4-331)
    Needs of Department of Applied Mechanics and Experimental Engineering; local chapters of national fraternitites; Faculty travel
  - McBryde, J.M. 1916 (Box-folder 4-332)
  - McBryde Building 1915-1916 (Box-folder 4-333)
    Notable letterhead from H.W. Johns Manville Co.; Estimates; Letterhead of the Barrett Company; Letterhead of the Richmond Lumber Company, Inc.; Letterhead of Enochs Bros.; Letterhead of Nelson Hardware Company; Notable letterhead of the Farrar Lumber Company
  - McConnell, J.P. 1916 (Box-folder 4-334)
    State Normal School for Women, East Radford, Virginia
  - Mann, W.H., ex-governor 1916 (Box-folder 4-335)
  - Maphis, Charles G. 1916 (Box-folder 4-336)
  - Martin, Thomas S. 1916 (Box-folder 4-337)
  - Matthews, D.O. 1916-1917 (Box-folder 4-338)
    Walks, Street Lights, List of all lights in town to which college is furnishing free current
  - Military 1916-1917 (Box-folder 4-339)
    Notable letterhead from Coast Artillery School, Department of Engineering and Mine Defense, Fort Monroe
  - M-miscellaneous 1915-1916 (Box-folder 4-340)
    Letter from Manassas Industrial School for Colored Youth
  - Parrott, J.R. (Box-folder 4-341)
    Shops Department, Virginia Polytechnic Institute (1916); Department of Graphics, Virginia Polytechnic Institute
  - Polland, John G., Attorney General, Commonwealth of Virginia 1916 (Box-folder 4-342)
  - Price, H.L., Dean of Agriculture Department, Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station 1916 (Box-folder 4-343)
  - Priddy, Lawrence 1916 (Box-folder 4-344)
    Includes notable letterhead of Lawrence Priddy Insurance and notable letterhead from Wichita Mill and Elevator Company
  - Printing Plant 1916 (Box-folder 4-345)
  - Purcell, B.L. Dairy and Food Comissioner 1916 (Box-folder 4-346)
  - Randolph, L.S.; Engineer Experiment Station Bill 1916 (Box-folder 4-347)
    Includes notable letterhead of Hotel Continental
  - Republican Club 1916 (Box-folder 4-348)
  - Sanitation 1916, 1918 (Box-folder 4-348)
  - Saunders, W.D., Professor of Dairy Husbandry (Box-folder 4-350)
  - Schoene, W.J., Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station (Box-folder 4-351)
    Commonwealth of Virginia, Office of the State Crop Pest Commission
  - Reserve Troop Matters--James Hay 1915-1916 (Box-folder 4-352)
  - Shelton, Farras V. 1916 (Box-folder 4-353)
  - Shultz, J.H., Dining Hall Department 1916 (Box-folder 4-354)
  - Smyth, E.A., Department of Biology 1916 (Box-folder 4-355)
  - Stuart, Henry C., Commonwealth of Virginia, Governor's Office 1916 (Box-folder 4-356)
  - Starcher, G.C. 1914 (Box-folder 4-357)
  - Student--Whitmell Lathrop 1916 (Box-folder 4-358)
  - Swanson, Claude--Senator 1916 (Box-folder 4-359)
  - Vawter, C.E., Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Department of Physics 1916-1917 (Box-folder 4-359)
  - Wright, A.D., State School Inspector, Department of Public Instruction 1916 (Box-folder 4-361)
  - Athletic Council 1916, 1918 (Box-folder 4-362)
  - Ackley, S.A. 1919 (Box-folder 4-363)
  - Atkinson, Sallie J. 1918 (Box-folder 4-364)
  - A-Miscellaneous 1917-1919 (Box-folder 4-365)
    Office of the Registrar; Notable letterhead from Alphons Custodis Chimney Construction Company; Notable letterhead from America Lead Pencil Company
  - Barlow, W.E. 1917-1919 (Box-folder 4-366)
    Needs of the Department of Metallurgy and Metallography
  - Bells for Classes 1919 (Box-folder 4-367)
  - Bernier, Chas. A. 1918-1919 (Box-folder 4-368)
  - Black, Alexander 1918 (Box-folder 4-369)
    Condition of roads to the mines
  - "Uncle Bill" 1918-1919 (Box-folder 4-370)
    Includes business card from the Travelers Hotel
  - Bills--House and Senate 1919 (Box-folder 4-371)
    Industrial Commission of Virginia; Bills to provide vocational education; and Workers' compensation
  - Bryan, John Stewart 1918 (Box-folder 4-372)
  - Burr, Chas. G., State Agent in Charge of Boys' Clubs, Cooperative Extension Work 1917-1919 (Box-folder 4-373)
    Boys agriculture club
  - Byrd, H.F. 1918 (Box-folder 4-374)
    Coal car tracer; Pocahontas Coal Sales Company; United States Fuel Administration; Power Plant; Coal shipments; United States Railroad Administration; and Opening abandoned milk
  - Buruss, J.A. 1918-1919 (Box-folder 4-375)
    Correspondence regarding article about wheelbarrow to be sent to move plant to Charlottesville and Harrisonburg State Normal appropriations
  - B--Miscellaneous 1918-1919 (Box-folder 4-376)
    Icludes letterhead of Philadelphia Wood and Textile Association and George Bryan correspondence
  - Campbell Theo P., Dean of Faculty 1913-1919 (Box-folder 4-377)
  - J.P. Campbell Jr. (Registrars) 1919 (Box-folder 4-378)
    Student fees and protocol for reporting grades and absences
  - Cancelled Checks, Bills, Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station 1914-1918 (Box-folder 4-379)
    Waiters appointed for the session of 1917-1918
  - Military Department 1916-1919 (Box-folder 5-380)
    Search for commandant of cadets
  - ROTC 1917-1919 (Box-folder 5-381)
    Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Office of the Dean of Faculty; Office of the Treasurer
  - Corps--Unsatisfactory List 1915-1916 (Box-folder 5-382)
    Demerits
  - Dean's Report (Campbell) 1915-1918 (Box-folder 5-383)
    Dean of General Faculty; Statistics
  - Miscellaneous 1912, 1916-1918 (Box-folder 5-384)
    Virginia Agricultural Experiemtn Station; Notable letterhead from Troy Laundry Machine Company Ltd.; Notable letterhead from the Bugle, 1916; Certificate from the United States Food administration appointing Dr. Eggleston Director if Colleges and School, Blacksburg, for the Federal Food Administration for Virginia for the duration of World War I
  - War Training 1917-1918 (Box-folder 5-385)
    Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Office of the Treasurer; and notable letterhead from American Surety Company
  - Carneal and Johnston, Architects and Consulting Engineers 1913-1914 (Box-folder 5-386)
    Building renovations and erection of "shops"
  - VPI miscellaneous 1914 (Box-folder 5-387)
    Summer session proposed; College of William and Mary Summer session
  - Sophmore Court Matters 1913-1914 (Box-folder 5-388)
    Letterhead from the Bugle, 1914; Hazing
  - Williams, J.E. 1918 (Box-folder 5-389)
  - Telegrams 1917-1919 (Box-folder 5-390)
  - Students 1914, 1917-1919
    Student policy
  - Student Correspondence 1918 (Box-folder 5-392)
    Includes notable letterhead from Semora Supply Company
  - Student Army Training Corps Demobilization 1918 (Box-folder 5-393)
    Includes notable letterhead from the Jacobson Printing Company
  - Saunders, W.D., Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station 1917-1918 (Box-folder 5-394)
  - Salary Increases, Virginina Polytechnic Institute 1918 (Box-folder 5-395)
    Office of the Dean of Faculty; Library; Shops Department; and Office of the Treasurer
  - Rasche, W.H., Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Department of Graphics 1918-1919 (Box-folder 5-396)
  - P's 1918 (Box-folder 5-397)
  - Power House 1918-1919 (Box-folder 5-398)
  - Parrott, J.R., Director of Shops Department of the Virginia Polytechnic Institute 1918-1919 (Box-folder 5-399)
    Power plant; expenditures on new "shops;" and working hours
  - Paper Disposal 1919 (Box-folder 5-400)
  - Notices 1914, 1917-1918 (Box-folder 5-401)
  - Newman, C.M. 1918-1919 (Box-folder 5-402)
    Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Office of the Dean of Faculty; Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Department of English
  - Murray, T.J.--Resignation from Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station 1918 (Box-folder 5-403)
  - Military Service 1918 (Box-folder 5-404)
  - Miles, C.P. 1914, 1919 (Box-folder 5-405)
    Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Athletic Association; Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Department of Modern Languages; and Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Office of the President
  - J.P. McConnell 1918-1919 (Box-folder 5-406)
    State Normal School for Women
  - Matthews, Superintendent of Grounds and Buildings, Heat and Power, Electric Light Department, Water Works, Campus, Steam Laundry 1918 (Box-folder 5-407)
    Requests for repairs in college buildings, roads; and Coal orders
  - J.M. McBryde 1918-1919 (Box-folder 5-408)
  - L miscellaneous 1918-1919 (Box-folder 5-409)
    Commonwealth of Virginia, Dairy and Feed Division; Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Office of the President
  - J.B. Lucas 1918-1919 (Box-folder 5-410)
    Agricultural High School
  - Licenses--Explosives 1917-1918 (Box-folder 5-411)
    Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Department of Mining Engineering; Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Department of Chemistry and Chemical Engineering; and Department of Interior, Bureau of Mining
  - Lancaster, Dabney S. 1918-1919 (Box-folder 5-412)
    Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Department of Argricultural Education; Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Office of the Registrar
  - K-miscellaneous 1918-1919 (Box-folder 5-413)
  - George W. Koener 1918-1919 (Box-folder 5-414)
    Commonweath of Virginia, Department of Agriculture and Immigration
  - Leslie D. Cline 1917-1919 (Box-folder 5-415)
  - J-miscellaneous 1918-1919 (Box-folder 5-416)
    Treasury Department, Internal Revenue Service
  - T.C. Johnson 1918-1919 (Box-folder 5-417)
    Virginia truck experiment station
  - Johnson, J.S.A. 1918 (Box-folder 5-418)
    Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Department of Applied Mechanics and Experimental Engineering; Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station; Lecture rooms
  - Jewel, W.H. 1918-1919 (Box-folder 5-419)
    Norfolk and Western Railway Company; and controversy over L.L. Jewel's will
  - Jackson, James A. 1918-1919 (Box-folder 5-420)
    funds appropriated by General Assembly; Schenectady chapter of VPI Alumni Association
  - I--Miscellaneous 1918-1919 (Box-folder 5-421)
  - Inventories, Virginia Polytechnic Insitute 1912,1916-1919 (Box-folder 5-422)
    Virginia Agricultural Experiemtn Station; Office of the Registrar; Dining Hall Department; Commonwealth of Virginia, Bureau of Insurance; Office of D.O. Matthews, Superintendent of Grounds and Buildings, Heat and Power, Electric Light Department, Water Works, Campus, Steam Laundry; Office of the Commandant; Shops Department; Department of Civil Engineering; Department of Physics; Department of Applied Mechanics and Experimental Engineering; Department of Geology; Department of Biology; Office of the President; Department og Electrical Engineering; Department of Graphics; Department of Mechanical Engineering; Department of Veterinary Science; Office of the Treasurer; and Electric Light Department